siteexperts.com 2006-10-16

# SiteExperts.com Privacy Statement

**Home**  
 Around the Web   
 Free Newsletters   
 Daily Log

**Community**  
 Join SiteExperts  
 Logon SiteExperts   
 Member Profiles

**User Groups**  
 SiteExperts.com Forums   
  -All Discussions   
  -SiteExperts Feedback   
  -The Lounge   
  -Dynamic HTML   
  -Site Design/ Critiques   
  -HTML and CSS   
  -XML Technologies   
  -The Wireless Internet   
  -Internet Explorer   
  -Microsoft .NET   
  -The Server   
  -Job Market   
  -Technical Support   
 Client User Group   
 Server User Group

**Developer's Paradise**  
 Inside Techniques  
  -Cross Browser DHTML   
   ...More...   
 Outside Techniques   
 Developer Products   
 Product Reviews   
 Web Sites   
  **Submit Resource**

**High-Tech Jobs**  

**Site Tools**  
 Web Logs, Guest Books  

**Site Information**  
 Search   
 About SiteExperts   
 Advertising Information   
 Personal Assistant   

|  |  **SiteExperts.com Privacy Statement**  
Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we may use it. 

SiteExperts.com gathers two types of information about our users; data that users provide through optional site registration and aggregated tracking information derived mainly by analyzing the site's log files to help us better understand the demographics of our visitors. Since SiteExperts.com's revenue is derived mostly from advertising, this aggregate demographic data is essential to keep our service free. We never divulge individual user information to a third party without prior consent from the user. SiteExperts.com gathers the following specific user information. Anytime SiteExperts.com requests users to volunteer information, the purpose for the request will be clearly indicated. 

  * **Optional Community Registration**   
SiteExperts.com is a community-oriented site. To take part in the optional community features (posting messages and resources) we request users to register. The registration process requires a username, password, and e-mail address. Optionally, you can provide additional information about your place of residence, your interests, and subscribe to various newsletters. 

The only information that is displayed publically is your chosen user name. The user name is used with messages you post and resources you submit. Optionally, you can also choose to publish your interests by creating a user profile page. You can create and freely update your personal profile page at any time. Your e-mail address and other information is never provided publically or to third parties. The only exception which requires your consent is to receive contest or sweepstake prizes.

  * **Contests and Sweepstakes**   
Occasionally SiteExperts.com offers contests and sweepstakes to our visitors. In some cases the prizes may be shipped directly from a vendor. In these circumstances, you will receive a notification from SiteExperts.com asking permission to release your name and address so that you may receive the prize. Your permission must be received before your name and address will be made available to the vendor. 

Because the rules and terms of each contest can vary, we post an information page about the contest for the duration of the event. 

  * **Newsletters**   
SiteExperts.com offers e-mail newsletters. To subscribe to a newsletter you must opt-in at the time of registration or by supplying your e-mail address on the subscription form. At any point, you can unsubscribe or change your subscription status by emailing [Newsletters@SiteExperts.com.com](mailto:Newsletters@SiteExperts.com.com). When subscribing to a newsletter, you can be assured that your e-mail address will never be used to send you unrequested promotional material. 
  * **Surveys**   
Occasionally SiteExperts.com may conduct a user survey to gather demographic data about our audience. The aggregate results of this data may be shared with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party. 
  * **Usage tracking**  
SiteExperts.com tracks traffic patterns throughout the site. We never correlate this information with data about individual users. When a visitor requests a page, our server automatically recognizes the browser version, platform, and the IP address. The domain names and IP addresses are collected to aggregate information on what pages users access or visit. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals. 
  * **Cookie**   
A _cookie_ is a small file that can be written and accessed by the site that creates them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read information from your hard drive or a cookie created by another site. SiteExperts.com uses cookies as follows: 
    * Advertisement Tracking: SiteExperts.com delivers a cookie to track advertisement delivery. We do not associate this information with the individual user. 
    * Automatic Log-on (SmartLogin): Visitors can optionally choose to be automatically logged into the site when visiting the home page. When this option is enabled, a cookie is saved containing a user identifier and an encrypted password. This information is used to verify your identity on your next visit. This cookie is only created when Smart-Login is enabled by the visitor. 
    * Log-in Status: When you log onto SiteExperts.com we create a temporary cookie containing an identifier. This ensures that the web-site knows you are logged in as you browse the site. This cookie automatically expires after a period of time or you close your browser. This cookie is only used to keep you logged into the site and is not associated with the pages you visit. 

Please direct any questions about the SiteExperts.com Privacy Policy to Privacy@SiteExperts.com.
